YVETTE JOHNSON-RODGERS

Albuquerque, New Mexico | (505) 859-6496 <u>itsyvejr@gmail.com</u> | <u>www.yvette.io</u> | GitHub: Yvejr

SUMMARY

After working closely with technology for the last ten years, I decided to go further into the digital world by actually creating apps and web pages for other people to use. I started by teaching myself HTML and CSS, and really enjoyed the combination of using a concrete computer language to accomplish a creative goal in the form of live, interactive content. I decided to make this a career change and joined Deep Dive Coding, a 10 week long intensive coding bootcamp. I look forward to developing for a local Albuquerque tech company, where I can bring my positive attitude and client first mindset.

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

Computer Languages: Angular, Bootstrap, CSS3, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery, MySQL, PHP and PHPUnit

Operating Systems: Windows: XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1; iOS, Android

Software: Microsoft Office, G Suite, Adobe PS LightRoom

Troubleshooting: Desktop and laptop computers, mobile devices, and wired, wireless, and cellular networks

People Skills: Leadership, Public Speaking, Training, Coaching, Customer Service, Technical Support

Other Skills: Knowledge of design patterns, command line scripting

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

Deep Dive Coding Fullstack Bootcamp

Expected June 2018

The University of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM

2007-2014

Bachelor of Arts in Communication, focus in Interpersonal Communication Minor in Psychology

Tech Skills Network+ Class

June 2016

COMPTIA A+ Certification

May 2010

RECENT EXPERIENCE

Verizon 2008-2018

Customer Service

Handled customer concerns while balancing the needs of the business such as average handle time, financial credits, and sales goals.

Tech Support

Supported customer base in all mobile operating systems, computers using the cellular network, and voice services for all phones. I continued to sharpen my support and customer interaction skills.

Coach

Provided on the job training and support for agents new to the Tech Support role. I updated and later re-created new materials for daily and weekly focus for the 6 week program.

Leadership

Participated in a year long leadership development program, honing my leadership skills and practicing them as center and team support. One side project was collaboratively identifying needs for additional supplemental training and employee engagement programs, then developing and delivering them to large groups. I then spent six months in an active leadership role as a Supervisor, managing two teams total, of 10 people and 15 people respectively.

Bode Aviation 2006-2008

Facilities Maintenance

Maintained cleanliness, detailing aircraft, and assisted with remodeling and moving locations of the business.

Fixed Base Operations

Marshalled and re-fueled aircraft, worked the front desk for reservations, billing, and other customer needs.

COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

Reading Works, Inc. 2014 - Present

Adult Tutor for Literacy and High School Equivalency Exam